( Watch on kissasia.biz or asiankh.org )
Where do I start? What I'm really trying to say is, -
- that everything I am is due to where I come from.
Eternia. A world of endless beauty.
All that only exists in myths and bedtime stories...
On Eternia, it's real.
Griffons, dragons, talking tigers.
Enchanted forests, scorching deserts, flying islands and much more.
Seriously, I'm not on drugs.
And then there's Castle Grayskull.
My father said that Eternia is the beating heart of the cosmos, -
- and that Grayskull is the heart of that heart.
And then the heart in the heart in that heart must -
- be the power of Grayskull.
It is said that it can make a person as powerful as a god.
To protect the power, it was enclosed in a casing.
An ancient sword called the Sword of Power.
I know, but that's what they could come up with.
It is said that when Eternia is in dire straits, -
- will a hero step forward and grab the sword -
- and, you know, use it...
Too wild.
Until then, it was guarded in the castle by the vigilant Sorceress.
She was wise and ancient -
- and a little scary, I think. But she's cool.
For centuries, Grayskull has been protected by my ancestors.
I come from a pretty impressive lineage of heroes.
Noble, strong, fearless.
Mom, I don't want to fight.
The others are bigger and stronger, and I have poor hand-eye coordination.
- Who told you that? - Cringer.
He is the smallest and the weakest.
It's a miracle he wasn't mutilated. Or killed.
So what should the prince do instead of weapons training?
Hang out and play with Cringer?
- I can play with a ball of yarn. - You're no help.
- Do I really need it? - Weapons training. Now.
Listen, you future adornments of Eternos.
No statues are erected of losers. No streets are named after losers.
And there are no parades because you do your best.
This place, this palace , and your entire life are created -
- of men and women who won their battles.
And as the King's Man-At-Arms , you may believe I have won many.
That's why we're here.
Because I saved your mom and dad's asses.
I saved your neighbor's ass and your neighbor's mom and dad's ass.
A lot of loot. The point is, I've fought for you.
And now you must fight for me with sharp reflexes, -
- unerring aim and magnificent muscle power.
And this one. Who knows what it is?
It's a stick.
Thanks for pointing out the obvious.
Second commandment? Teela?
- Your weapon. - Good girl.
They are your weapons. They are an extension of you.
Match two and two! I want to see some nice bruises.
I want to see bleeding noses and broken teeth.
Get started!
Dian, should we...?
Adam.
Look him in the eye when you slap him in the face.
- Parry, or I'll strike. - Can't we talk about it?
Adam, just do what you can.
Yes. Teela!
- What kind of friend are you? - The kind who beats you up.
Duncan.
How do you think the young people are doing?
They are skilled and diligent, sir.
- Everyone? - Don't dance, Adam.
Hit me! Hit me!
- He's making a fool of himself. - I'll make a man out of him.
Yes, but what kind of man?
Hit me now!
- He disarmed her then. - That's not how it works, old friend.
Boy.
Fight me with this.
Pick it up.
Well.
So defend yourself.
Far! Far!
This world is not a place for the weak.
Say it.
Adam, get up.
When you fall...
You have the chance to show your steadfastness. Okay?
Look strong. When he turns and sees you, -
- you have to show him that you can handle the must.
When he turns around, he shouldn't see a little boy.
He's going to see a man. What is he going to see?
- A man. - Good.
As soon as he turns around.
Let the disappointment go away.
The show is over! Back to work!
Adam.
- What are you doing? - Following you.
- I came up here to be alone. - Don't be such a squink.
I didn't think you were weak. During training today.
My father did.
Is it Sorceress?
What is she looking at?
King Randor, we are under attack.
I've got it under control, sir. The Life Guards are trained for this.
I promise nothing will happen to you or your family.
They will be escorted to Grayskull.
It'll be okay. Stick with me.
- Teela, come on. - Dad, I'm scared.
Who taught you that word? Not me. It'll be okay, pussy.
As long as I'm here, you have nothing to fear.
Come on.
Run! Run!
- There are too many of them. - A large army means one thing.
More goals.
Come, come.
After me!
This way.
You stay there.
Weak, little tin soldiers.
Sir, hurry away.
Let me handle this.
There is someone who wants to fight.
That's it and no further.
How dare you come here. Don't you know who I am?
Tell me.
I am Duncan, Commander of the Life Guards...
And the King's Man-At-Arms.
And today...
Have you failed?
Far! Far!
Come on, get up. Come on.
Teela, I have failed.
Come on.
Hold fast!
Randor's reign ends tonight.
You thought you were so strong that you stopped fearing what lurked in the shadows.
It was me.
I was lurking.
In the deepest and darkest corners of the universe I lurked.
But now I'm coming into the light...
And let you see your downfall.
Run. Don't look back.
Adam, don't be afraid. I got you.
Be strong, my boy. I 'll hold them down. Run.
Far!
- What do you want to do to me, you un-German? - I just want to chop your head off.
Regardless of my fate, Eternos will never be yours!
Your palace is just stone and glass.
Your crown is a costume.
I want the power behind it.
Evil-Lyn.
Oh, Evil-Lyn.
How poetic, Prince Skeletor.
Take him away. He's finished.
When the day dawns, Eternia will witness my greatness!
- That was it. - Yes, of course.
When I raise my clenched fist, I'm done. That's my crescendo!
It's noted, sir.
They are coming. Grayskull will fall.
No, it will pass. Take the sword to me, child.
Now, quickly.
You must bring the sword to safety somewhere far away from here.
Let it be a place where they will never find him. My home.
Adam, take care of yourself.
And never forget where you come from.
That sword is mine.
- Give it to me, boy. - Don't you dare!
Tender!
Yes, I dare.
You must not lose the sword. It is your only way home.
You carry the hope of Eternia with you. Go!
Off you go!
No!
So that's how I ended up in -
- Oklahoma City.
What about you, Julie? Is your family from here?
Excuse me, did you say "Skeleton"?
Yes, I did.
I have to take it.
- It hasn't rung. - I have to take it and go.
Julie, sorry.
I know it sounds crazy. Was that the thing with the sword?
The sword is really just a sheath for the power.
Like this cup.
Now the cup holds the power of Grayskull.
But instead of the cup, it was my sword, and I dropped it.
I'm not proud of it, but I lost it.
I'll find it, and then it will show me the way home.
Are you breaking up with me?
No. They belong together.
Yes.
You mustn't do that. You don't mean it.
What's up, bro? You're home early.
I don't want to talk about it.
Did you tell her? The whole thing?
Sorceress, the talking green tiger, the king father's disappointment in your laxity?
Yes. I probably should have left that part out.
When you say you're from another planet and a magic sword can get you home, -
- then you sound a little bit very crazy.
- Your drawings of chopped iron... - They are chopped in reality.
She asked where I was from. What should I have said?
That your parents died in a tragic accident, -
- and that you suppress it with a fantasy. Just like your psychologist says.
Should I forget who I am and the whole purpose of my life?
Maybe the purpose of your life is just not to be weird. Have you considered that?
Can't you just go to work, pay the rent, live for the weekend -
- and counting the days until your next vacation?
Like everyone else.
The task was to draw a historical figure.
Ram Man is historical.
Nothing.
It's going to be a good day.
I hear you emotionally.
I feel you with your consent.
I see you for who you are.
Remind yourself of that with our favorite mantra.
Let's stand up and say it together.
Everyone.
"I have the power -
- to be the best version of myself."
So his truth is not my truth.
We just have to agree on whose truth we are talking about.
I sense that truth-telling is underway.
But perhaps a little bit of truth-listening would be constructive .
Hvabehar?
You have taken my place.
- You're taking my place. - You must apologize for that.
Do you have any good advice for a beginner? You know, some words of wisdom.
You should place yourself behind yourself, not in front. The front is a facade.
But when you back yourself , there is nothing you cannot achieve.
Fat.
Well said.
- Could you repeat that? - No. You won't get any more.
Good luck, kid.
HAVE YOU SEEN THIS SWORD?
Ding-dong!
Hey! Do you have time for a quick chat in my office?
I'm in the middle of some super important HR stuff right now.
I can see that.
But it wasn't really a question. More of an order.
The tone was also confusing. Is that a question or not?
It's not. Ten minutes?
Okay, Suzie.
Adam, have you given any thought to your future here at the company?
Should I?
Let me tackle it from a different angle.
You are good at your job. You are kind, honest, thoughtful.
People listen to you. You are well-liked.
But you seem absent.
I could not dream that these other people's joys, -
- and if your joy is geeky things and swords, it's just cannonade.
But it's also my job to give you a little date spanking.
- Date spanking? - A rascal, you know.
Now I'm the strict boss, not the fun friend.
But put on your serious hat. Your hobby goes beyond your work.
I found your sword.
Let's ignore it for a moment.
Your obsession with swords doesn't look good in the HR department.
I'm going to have to fire you if you don't get your act together.
So it's an ultimatum?
Yes. You got it. Conflicts are not my strong suit.
You'll be fired if you don't stop staring at guns.
You scare people. Especially Darryl.
I hate Darryl.
You don't understand. I 'm nothing without that sword.
Okay, moment of truth. Do you want to live here in the real world?
Or will you piss your life away like a daydreamer without a goal -
- and without the ability to put the phone down?
- I just need to see what it says. - No, leave it alone.
Don't. Okay, you did it.
Found your sword. You can have it for $300.
Adam?
- Adam? - I have to go.
If you leave now, you can kiss this place goodbye. With consent.
I think I'm here.
Meet me inside.
- How do I know...? - You just know.
It's you, right?
I think so.
- Coolest. - Yes.
- Do you have my sword? - No, I don't think so.
No sword?
The best.
Then you are not you.
Sorry.
- Do you have my sword? - What?
Forget it.
Do you have my sword?
It's me.
Have you asked the whole store if they have your sword?
- They look like someone with a sword. - I have a wizard's wand at home.
Leave him alone.
I can't take you any further.
What?
What can I use it for?
That's your problem, buddy. I've never been here.
The situation is under control!
Hey, you can't do that.
Don't worry, it's my sword.
- Please leave Torak alone. - Torak is standing on me.
- Stop harassing him. - He's the one harassing me.
- The sword is not for sale. - I just intend to take it.
In a moment I will disappear in a flash of brightly colored light.
- Or something like that. - The bladder.
By the power of Grayskull! I have -
- need to get home!
Grayskull, take me home now.
Are you single?
What the hell are you doing?
I hate when you make me laugh. And when you make me cry.
- Is that...? - The power sword. Yes, that's it.
Act now.
Do something.
FAR
Although.
Cool sword, Highlander.
Yes, blistered sword, Rip Van... King Arth...
What kind of person are you, Highlander?
What now? Idiots.
Stay seated.
What's going on?
Adam?
- Is it really you? - What?
Don't you know me?
You're still a squink.
Have you been?
Are you ready to return home?
- What does that beast want from me? - He's after this.
The sword sent a signal. Why didn't you raise it?
- I kind of misplaced it. - Misplaced it? It's been 15 years.
Okay, I'll count to three.
- One, two... - I can't.
Three!
- Jump! - No!
What's wrong with you?
- Where are we going? - To my ship. Up there.
Where up?
Cell.
- Ship, open up. - Opening the access hatch.
I told you it was real!
Not you specifically, -
- but you also represent those in my life who doubted me.
Come on!
- Ship, get us out of here now. - Get us out of here now.
Hold on. It's running away now.
- Ship, fold the space. - Fold the space and run away.
I can't believe it's you.
Yes, it's me.
You have become so big.
Because you are old.
With grace. You've grown up.
And you haven't changed one bit.
You have no idea how bad things are . Everything has changed in your absence.
My parents?
Skeletor took them that night, -
- and we haven't seen them since.
Arriving in Eternia in ten...
Nine, eight, seven...
- To think that I'm finally home. - Better lower your expectations.
Two, one.
It's all gone.
Skeletor didn't care about Eternos.
He just didn't want others to have it.
- Why did he do it? - Because he's evil.
It must go deeper than that.
He has a skull face.
We have to leave. It's dangerous to be here.
- What are you staring at? - I didn't know you were awake.
- Get my staff, you pig. - Sure.
If you drop it, I'll make sausage out of you.
Just like your mother.
First Skeletor.
The beast has returned.
O vile and cruel Skeletor, you sadistic king of evil...
Oh, shut up. Get down on your knees.
Lower. Lower.
Lower.
Do you have the sword?
I found it, but Teela took it. That really hurts, sir.
- Teela? - Man-At-Arms' lineage.
Her ship was spotted over Eternos this morning.
Then the sword is here. We must let her shadow.
It's already being done, sir.
Why are you still here? Get me that sword, you untalented woolly tomboy!
What am I, Evil-Lyn? Am I not powerful?
Lord, you are the most powerful.
Have I not shown the people of Eternia that I am a just and worthy ruler?
- By killing them by the thousands. - But what is it worth?
Sir, with your permission...
You have already won. You have a huge army at your disposal.
You have your Chaos Staff, your Bone Throne...
You have me.
- Do you need more? - It can all be taken from me.
My staff can be taken from me, and so can you. And what am I then?
- Lord... - Then I am nothing!
As long as someone else carries the sword, my power is only temporary.
I must have more than fleetingness. I am no petty king.
I am a devil, but I want to be a god.
- Where are you taking me? - To the Life Guards.
What's left of us.
- Are the Life Guards hiding here? - Skeletor isn't looking for us here.
And now that we have the sword, we can defeat him.
Take good care of it and avoid attracting attention.
Do people walk around dressed like this on Earth?
No, not really.
Don't stare.
The sword is located.
Let me take the floor. You may be a little dissatisfied with...
Where have you been? It's teeming with Skeletor's lackeys.
I have found the Sword of Power.
What?
There. And the man who carries it is King Randor's son.
The missing prince of Eternos.
Hello.
It is a great honor to be here.
- He's no king's son. - Yes. And he can prove it.
Yes, I can.
DRIVING LICENSE
I remember as a child seeing you in charge of combat training.
Is it an earthquake?
- Who is that little louse? - Ram Man?
- What did you call me? - Ram Man.
I called you that because you look like a...
But what?
A man who rams.
- Deceiver. You don't know us. - Yes, I do.
I've been telling people about you my whole life.
As a child, I made drawings of you.
- Did you do it? - Yes.
Who am I then?
You are Fisto.
That's not your real name, but you fist people.
I don't fist people.
- I saw you punch a goblin once. - Was he supposed to be the savior of Eternia?
I was expecting something else too, but I swear it's him.
I tracked down the Power Sword, and it led me to...
Stand still!
Too.
- Thank you. - It went terribly.
- We need to discuss this. - Yes, let's discuss it.
- Your name is Dina, right? - Dian.
Dian, well, that's so sweet. We went to school together.
You always pushed me into the lockers.
Did it work?
Dian? You must have locked it. By accident.
- Fisto? - Because he has a huge...
- I was ten years old. - We have to get out of here.
It smells like a urinal here.
- That's him. - Get off.
As you wish.
Is it a Class 4 Battlebot?
No, it's just a service bot. An overdeveloped maid.
Class 4 are deadly super soldiers.
Just one of them is equal to 15 soldiers.
- Closer to 20. - The bladder.
It resembles the Sword of Power.
- It's smaller than I thought. - It's because my hand is so big.
Your big hand is the other hand.
This one is also quite big. That's why the sword seems so small.
Caught!
- Come on. - We may have a problem.
They're coming to take the sword. We have to get out of here.
Miss, you're not cut out to wash floors. Come with us.
- As a servant? - No, as a soldier.
Stop messing with household appliances.
I agree. But I refuse to cook or do laundry.
And any kind of fluids that might come out of you are your problem.
Wait. One moment.
- We can't leave him behind. - That drunkard?
Dad, wake up.
- Why did you call him dad? - He's my dad. Dad, wake up.
- Quiet, I'm sleeping. - Duncan?
- Can you help? - Yes.
Cross, he's heavy.
Good idea. He needs to hydrate.
Who is he? Do I know you?
Yes.
When I was a child, you trained me.
Sword fighting, fist fighting...
You scolded me, kicked me, belittled me, and shattered my self-confidence.
Adam. My name is Adam.
- I'm not wiping it up. - You weren't asked to either.
Now I know who you are. You are Randor's son.
Yes, it's me.
- Sweet, little Adam. - Great, you remember me.
- Spliced. Soft. Weak. - I guess I wasn't soft.
We have to go. Come on, Dad.
No, no, I'm fine here. I'll stay here until I throw up.
We have to carry him.
Aha. Thank you so much for taking me on this exciting adventure.
I can walk by myself!
This way.
The sword is here. Find it!
Get the sword as far away from him as possible.
Come with me.
What's going on?
Hey, snot robot! I can walk by myself.
- You better duck. - You better shut the f...
Roboto, won't you turn on the battle mode?
- Are you trying to be funny? - Duncan reprogrammed her.
- She almost blew my mind. - It was a malfunction.
Run.
- What the hell is going on? - Stop shooting at me!
Skids!
After me!
- Did she jump? - I didn't expect that.
- Should I carry Drunkman? - Duncan, are you okay?
I'm at the top.
- How did he avoid dying? - I'll be fine.
Come on.
- Come forward, you crooks! - Trap Jaw.
- Who? - From my drawings.
Oh no, no, no, no...
- Everyone but him. - You can't get away!
Let me talk to him. Start a dialogue.
- What? A dialogue? - I often do that at work.
I'm actually pretty good at it. I'll be right back.
Hello!
Good day.
Mr. Trap Jaw. Hello.
Vent.
Can I talk to you for a moment? I 'd like to de-escalate the situation.
It feels as if the moods have turned completely upside down.
Now, so they are?
- And who are you? - I'm Adam...
Okay. I can see we 're moving into troubled waters.
Be quiet.
Okay, but conflict resolution depends on effective communication.
- Use the sword! - What kind of sword?
Say the words.
By...
By the power of Grayskull.
By the power of Grayskull!
I have the power!
Wow.
Champion of Grayskull. We are saved.
We are finished.
That's what I taught you! It's fucking good.
We have to see how we move forward.
Did you see that? I ripped his arm off and shot all his friends.
I saw it.
You fools! You douchebags and douchebags!
Master...
You primitive, beatable pissants! I want that sword. Do you hear?
It's mine. Mine, mine, mine, mine, mine!
I want it. Do you hear?
And you must get it for me.
- Is that understood?! - After them! Get the sword!
- Let me control. - Don't talk about it.
- You're doing great, Teela. - Not now, Adam.
- Run me through... - Cracks in the hull.
Ship, perform analysis.
- Analysis: My hull is cracked. - Received.
- I have a lot of experience with... - Would you like to get off and leave?
Bad.
Shoot them down. Take the Cloud Sled.
- I'm on my way. - Not you. Absolutely not you.
What now?
We are losing altitude.
- If you let go... - Not a word.
We can't do it.
- Keep the ship steady. - Says the drunkard.
Adam?
Adam!
Behind you!
- Move, you shovel! - What?
You will be killed!
You're really good at flying.
May I be free?
Troublemakers!
Your long respite is now over. You are out.
If you wish to see tomorrow, I hereby demand your allegiance.
Do you know what that means, criminal?
That means I'm going to kill you one by one, -
- until you tell me the name of the arrogant barbarian.
You know who I mean.
Muscles, loincloth, tanned -
- and a large, shiny sword.
No?
Well then.
You.
Evil-Lyn, who is it?
- Moss Man. - He's on it.
Now, O fallen heroes of Eternia, behold how he begs for his pitiful life.
Be well. Please.
The best.
Look, my own. I made compost.
It was good.
I'll try again.
Who is the warrior who fought for you today?
- Stop. I'll say it. - Let me hear it.
It is the young prince, risen from the dead.
Well, so that's it?
Take them away, lock them up, and set this place on fire!
They're not following us here.
- Not without backup. - I have to look for Adam.
No, leave it to me. Teela, I can handle it.
Could. You could do it, honey. I'll fix it. Stay here.
PERSIAN
Where am I?
Who am I?
You are the one who will bring peace to Eternia.
Champion of Grayskull.
Adam.
- Zodac, I swear you're alive. - You chased the Sorceress away.
- It's not Sorceress. - I think it was.
Sure.
- Have you come across anything? - Oddly enough, not.
Well.
Come on. It's getting dark soon.
We'll stay here until tomorrow morning.
What is it?
I just haven't seen you in such a long time.
- Man-At-Arms is in here somewhere. - I hope you find him.
Listen, just a moment.
What do we have here?
- Who wants a dram? - Dad, seriously?
Now sit down.
Let's have a little one and sing a few songs. The victory must be celebrated.
What kind of victory?
- That we didn't die. - You call that a victory?
- We've earned it. - You've earned it for 15 years.
Then there's more for the two of us. Come and sit down.
Cheers to the sword -
- and for Grayskull's champion.
Tearing a man's arm off is not really something to celebrate.
It was you or him.
What happened to being understanding and listening -
- and talk together?
Talk together? What do you do when someone attacks your family?
Should I answer that I am going to fight?
You're protecting them. You don't understand.
You frown at the shooting-crazy footmen.
But in war, it's not the poets who step in. It's the muscleman.
And he doesn't do it to win honors.
He does it so his children can see tomorrow.
It's a man's people in my eyes.
He shows steadfastness when he is needed.
Just like you did.
And speaking of which, you didn't do it that crazy at all.
That's the nicest thing you 've ever said to me.
The execution was just a little sloppy, and your technique needs to be polished.
There we have the Duncan I remember.
Will you give me a hand?
It's quite heavy, so please...
I'll get your loincloth in... Excuse me.
Well, how does it feel to be the mighty warrior?
All things considered, it feels pretty cool.
But I have no idea what became of my shirt. Or my pants.
Will they come back or do I have to buy new ones every time?
I've really missed you.
In a straight way.
I thought about you. All the time.
Not a day went by that I didn't think about you.
In a straight way.
And on how much...
Our friendship means.
You were just such a good friend. Almost like a little brother.
You are and will always be my friend. Nothing can change that.
Phew!
We have to confiscate that pocket lark before my father starts singing.
Yes, we can't have that.
Insignificant underdogs, it's me, Skeletor.
In death too, get under my heel.
He called us teddy bears.
But one of you thinks he's something special.
The lost prince has apparently returned.
But it's not your Eternia anymore, Prince Adam.
It is mine, with all that it contains. That also applies to the sword you carry.
It is made for a far mightier hand than yours.
So here is my generous offer.
Bring the Sword of Power to Snake Mountain and you will be reunited with -
- mother and father.
Yes, they are alive and well.
Not too well, but they're alive.
Imagine, you will be able to become a happy family again.
Or they could die a cruel death.
And it will forever be your fault.
How heavy will that sword feel, you champion of Grayskull?
I have to go. Now.
Adam, it's a trap. If Skeletor gets the sword, he'll become invincible.
He won't get the sword. I'll kill him with it.
- You can't just charge in. - I have godly powers in my hands.
But you're just a man.
He has my family, Teela. I have to save them.
That's what a man's people do.
- Now you sound like my father. - Is that so bad?
- It will be seen. - I'll do it with or without you.
Adam...
We are with you.
To the bitter end.
- You'd think they'd want to die. - Not now.
Come on. This is the road to Snake Mountain.
We don't know what's in there.
I'm in there.
Do as I do.
Hi, I'm Adam, -
- Prince of Eternia and defender of the secrets of Castle Grayskull, -
- and I carry the Sword of Power.
Hand over your weapon.
I will give the sword to Skeletor and only to Skeletor.
Keep your sword. Guards!
Take him and his amazing muscles to Prince Skeletor.
The rest will follow me. Get ready in the dungeon.
Adam, give him a scratch!
Magnificent view, isn't it?
You just have a moment.
Far?
Adam? Is that you?
Yes. It's me.
The tearful reunion can wait. Then give me the sword.
Release him.
- I said it first. - Let him go!
Let's not play that game, kid. I play to win, and...
I'm cheating.
Take it!
Just try.
Beautiful, Evil-Lyn. He's frozen.
A fine display, Prince Adam. But to what use?
Fight me, face to face.
I don't have a face, and I don't care.
Besides, it's my turn to give a demonstration.
What does dad say?
Should I let him watch as I slaughter you with his sword?
Ah yes.
No!
Far?
Adam...
Let me look at you.
You were there.
You were late, but you came back.
I have changed so much.
I'm not a weak little boy anymore.
Now I am everything you wanted me to be.
What did I want you to be?
Another.
No, that wasn't... That wasn't what I wanted.
As a child, you were so incredibly small.
World...
Seemed too big for you.
That's why I tried to make you strong -
- to protect you.
It was the only way I knew.
There were so many things I should have said.
Dad, it's okay.
It's okay.
I wish I had understood you better.
I wish I had let you...
Be yourself.
Dad, no. Wait, wait, wait.
Don't close your eyes yet.
I haven't been told that yet.
I need you to hear me say it.
And so you both succumbed.
- Are you okay? - You've transformed back.
Tender.
He is dead.
How long have I waited.
Now I want to be reborn...
And the universe shall tremble in my shadow.
By the power of Grayskull.
I -
- has -
- the power!
Did I say the words wrong?
No, they were right enough. Try it with a little conviction.
Be your mouth, woman.
Why doesn't it work?
- Tell me why it doesn't work. - There's a ritual I can perform.
We must return the sword to its altar at Grayskull.
I promise, it works.
It just has to be.
Prepare my ship!
Hey, kid. You want to talk about it?
Adam, I'm not very good at...
To talk about...
What's going on inside. You know, those...
- Feelings? - Yes, that.
But one thing I know. I know what it feels like to fail.
To experience that you are not who you thought you were.
She better think I'm an old pacifier, worth saving, -
- than an old man who is worthless.
I let her down.
I failed you, Adam.
I promised to protect you all...
And I couldn't.
Do you remember what you said, -
- when I was beaten as a child?
Yes. I said, "Do 20 push-ups."
No. You said:
"You have to get up -
- and be steadfast."
Maybe we should try it together.
What do you say?
I'm in on that.
Hello.
There is someone who wants to greet you.
Cringer?
Can I lick you now?
Yes, okay.
- I've missed you. - To think you're here.
We are all here. All the heroes of Eternia.
Adam, are you okay?
Yes, I think so.
To assemble! There is a council of war!
Not a council of war, just a seminar.
- Okay. There's a war seminar! - Can I have your attention?
I'd like to take a moment to brainstorm an escape strategy.
- What? - Is that a fire speech?
- It's team building. - Who is he?
- I am Adam, Prince of Eternia. - Just a moment.
- I thought Adam was dead. - Wrap the neck away and let him talk.
Not dead. As you can see, I am very much alive.
Speak louder.
While I was on Earth, I learned, -
- that success in the workplace cannot be attributed to one man. Or woman.
Or whatever it is.
This is achieved by collaborating.
- Workplace? - We're in a dungeon.
I know that.
I know most of you don't know me.
But I know you all.
Mekaneck, the heroic human periscope.
And Ram Man. You ram.
- And you're a man. - Damn it!
- And Fisto, you fist people. - Exactly!
And Diane.
You pushed me into the lockers as a kid.
- Gu, I did. - I know you all.
I have carried you in my heart. Eternia is a part of me.
This is my home and I will fight for it.
But I can't do it alone. I need your help.
It was sheer luck that got us here.
But we can change that by working together.
We must put ourselves behind ourselves.
Not in front. The front is just a facade.
But when we back ourselves up...
There is nothing we cannot achieve.
Together.
So now we're taking back our home. Together!
- Hooray for Alan! - Alan!
So my name is Adam.
Adam.
But what can we do? The bars are made of photonium. Nothing can break them.
The walls are made of stone.
Ram Man.
Everyone. I have one question:
How much can you bench?
- What does "benches" mean? - Oh my God...
Kill anyone who comes close. Women and children...
First. Good boy.
Come, Evil-Lyn. The end is near.
Do you think you can make her battle-ready again?
Last time she tried to kill me.
- It was an accident. - She says that every time.
- I trust her, so... - Okay, fine.
You're not going to murder me, okay?
Have you had it on you the whole time?
And now there's no point in killing me.
I didn't promise anything.
Magnificent!
Okay, now!
- I can't breathe! - My lungs are burning!
They are fleeing!
Okay, you dirty skull-scrapers. Where are you hiding the ships?
They are coming.
Roboto and I will hold them down while you do what you have to do.
Are you sure you can handle it?
No, I'm not sure, but I'll do my best.
I know you want to.
You are so strong. Stronger than I have ever been.
You are the man I wish I could be.
- Uh, thanks? - Come here.
I love you. It was really beautiful.
Adam, we are right in the middle of a reconciliation.
You better get going.
Okay. That was nice. A nice moment between the three of us.
Okay, let's go.
Can you back out in time? Shouldn't I be wearing armor? This seems dangerous.
- Squeaky. - Teela, honestly.
He's not a whiner. He's a Battle Cat.
No, I'm not.
Okay, this one time. Climb up.
Next time I'll wear armor.
Then you have to fist it through!
Knock them out, Ram Man!
Sorry.
Enemies!
Now I'm going to show you how a real man uses his power.
No!
Defend yourself, witch.
Shouldn't we both just walk away and let them fight?
Forget it.
You are your father's daughter.
I am so.
- Now we're crashing their party. - I have the invitation right here.
If you have an invitation, it's not...
Answers requested! I'm going to kick those assholes.
You're really ruining the party metaphor.
Isn't that cool?
They won't be allowed into the castle as long as I'm standing upright.
You could barely stand on your feet.
Do you have more missiles?
- Yes, one. - That's plenty.
Yes!
What is it?
Run, run!
Be careful!
Duncan?
Do you remember me? Do you remember who I was?
The commander of the Life Guards and the king's Man-At-Arms.
But today...
I am a new person.
- Duncan? - Roboto.
- You can't shut down. - It doesn't matter.
Existence is just absurdities followed by infinite nothingness.
Talented girl.
Stand still, you muscular beast. I'm trying to destroy you!
You can just see there.
Your sword is worthless. Just a cheap toy.
That can't be right.
Now I'm curious. Without that, what are you?
Who are you? Let's find out.
- Give it a full load of garbage. - Sick flex, bro.
Honestly, Adam, I never bought that hormone-pumped barbarian look.
I guess you've never been tough . You were probably more of a wimp.
And those who didn't bully you felt sorry for you.
Want.
That wasn't the case.
Not that?
- So how was it? - What?
On your home planet. How was it there?
There was...
It was beautiful there.
Beautiful like nothing else.
No, have you ever been to Sedona?
This place is more you. A world in gray and beige -
- filled with eternal, humiliating defeats.
Adam, can this wait? I have a MUS conversation with Darryl.
- Who is that demon? - He destroyed my sword.
You and your sword...
While I conquered an entire planet, you sat here and...
- What is this? - The HR department.
Hospitality departments?
Adam, you naughty boy.
You can go and play with all your huge muscles -
- and the big, long sword dangling between your labile thighs.
But you will always be a loser. Eternia is not your home.
It's a dream about something you are not.
And that dream...
Is over.
Man! Man!
Adam?
Hey, Adam...
- Are you okay? - Yes.
I'm probably just dead.
Oh, that was worse. Let me know if you need anything.
You must have lost something.
Be well.
Quite convenient to die just before the rent is due to drop.
I'll probably pay for it.
- Stand up. - You're a talking bird.
- Yes. - How sour.
- You had a talking cat. - Fair point.
Is it over now?
- Am I dead? - Maybe.
Get up.
- But I'm dead. - You have the power.
The best.
Not anymore.
- The sword is broken. - What sword?
The power sword.
Well, that. What's up with that?
It is the Sword of Power.
"To him who carries the sword shall be given power."
When you raise your sword, what words do you say?
- "By the power of Grayskull." - Yes. Go ahead.
"I have the power."
Namely. You have the power, not the sword.
You. I chose you.
In the hands of ancient champions, power has been brute force.
But in yours it is so much more.
It is empathy. It is compassion.
It is humanity.
That's why I made you its sheath.
I am covered.
Now you are ready.
By the power of Grayskull.
I have the power!
Downturn.
Skeletor...
I have a suggestion.
Shouldn't we -
- put an end to the violence and talk together?
Just talk.
You have devastated my world and caused so much suffering.
Maybe because you didn't become king.
Maybe you didn't get enough love as a child.
It's not important who you are. What's important is what you do.
So do the right thing now.
Oh, you idiot.
You muscle-swelling slob. There's nothing right to do here.
There is nothing good in me that you can uncover.
There is nothing you can say that will change my nature, because I...
Is...
A villain.
And uh, how good it feels!
You're just a weak child.
It's possible you have the power, but you don't dare use it.
And you can't even.
I can use it.
I'd just rather not.
Is that all you have in you?
I stopped again.
Do you want to talk? What should we talk about?
That time has passed.
Up with you, squink.
Be well.
Not.
HALF A YEAR LATER
It was cool when you took his dick...
Well, what do you think?
It is a little bit well dialed down.
- Hi, Adam. - Hi.
How are you doing with your...
Emotions and such?
Nice.
Just know that if you ever need to talk, -
- then I'm here.
Fat.
Or if you want to lay down your arm.
Or if you want to scratch with a stick, I'm here too.
In a straight way.
Eternia's mightiest.
Look there. All those heroes you drew as a kid.
Ram Man, Fisto...
And what did you call him there?
- It's Mekaneck. - Annoying.
Did you give me a name too?
Warrior Goddess.
I was just a child.
- It's strong. - Don't put too much into it.
Did you give yourself a name too? You did. Tell us.
- You're just laughing. - Tell it anyway.
He-Man.
- What? - He-Man.
- That's terrible. - What does that mean?
It means a strong man. A masculine guy.
- Is that too macho? - No, no.
That's very manly. Just like you are.
What do you think?
Sure, man. That's...
Cell.
Cool to see that it wasn't me who was crazy.
I'm standing here with a green tiger. How wild is that?
But thank you for picking me up to prove it was all real.
My red light. I'm receiving a distress signal from an avion village.
That sounds like a task for He-Man.
He-Man.
Yes, I'll go and fix that.
Over there.
- Cringer. - Do we need to?
- Is he running out to change? - Yep.
Does he think we've forgotten? Everyone knows it.
We could also just look away if that would be easier.
No, let him do as he wants.
In today's story we saw, -
- that muscles don't necessarily make you a man.
And that if you have a skull face, then it's pretty safe, -
- that you are the villain. See you later!
I had given up hope.
For both of them.
Maybe she'll return one day too.
Felt traps Adora?
No. Not anymore.
You've probably seen better days.
Translation: Henrik Thøgersen Scandinavian Text Service